https://www.sandhillwholesale.com/privacy_notice-i-12.html?osCsid=bf55cde743b7920ee048622780d711dd

Products
Catalytic Combustors & AccessoriesRepair & Maintenance ProductsChimney Fans & Draft InducersFans, Controllers & Registers
Gas Appliances, Gas Logs & AccessoriesGas Vent Systems & ComponentsHearth AccessoriesPellet Stove Chimney & Accessories
Prefab Chimney ( Class A)Rain/Chimney Caps and DampersSingle & Double-Wall Black PipeHomeowners Choice Chimney Liner
Heatfab Saf-T Liner SystemVentinox® VFT Chimney LinerChimney Brushes & ToolsWood & Coal Stove Accessories
Checkout
The Oldest National Distributor of Fireplace, Wood and Gas Heating Products
Catalog
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or payment information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.
